pianu.com 2016-03-12

# Privacy Policy | Learn Piano Online - Pianu is an interactive website you can play with a real keyboard.

The use of the Website and/or Pianu’s Software Products and any other related websites, software, upgrades or updates and all related services and special offers provided by Pianu are subject to the hereunder provisions of this Privacy Policy.:

General  
Pianu takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information, which we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information.

BY USING OR ACCESSING ANY OF PIANU’S WEBSITES OR DOWNLOADING AND USING THEIR SERVICES OR SOFTWARE PRODUCTS, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. PIANU MAY AMEND THIS POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME..

Collection of Information  
Personal Information: Use of certain features of the Service may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nick name (or other user ID) and a password. Use of Pianu’s Software Products may require submission of all reasonably necessary computer, server, and network information related to the use of the Software Product.

Non personally identifiable Information: Pianu may also collect or receive additional non personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the Pianu’s Services or Website(s), and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on Pianu’s Services and/or Website(s).  
Pianu may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non-personally identifiable technical information, when the website(s) and pages are visited or when the Pianu’s Services are used.

How is the information being used? The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by Pianu, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you ; to fulfill your requests for Services, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Service and/or website(s), offerings and advertisements presented on Pianu Service, email communication, website(s) and pages; and to help offer you other Services, programs, or services that may be of interest.

Any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties, unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. Pianu may use this information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about various groups of Pianu users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.  
Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures.

Cookies: Pianu may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Service and/or of Pianu.com website, including to operate and improve offerings through the Service and/or website; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Service, and/or website; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you.Additionally, Pianu or its advertisers may use other companies, known as third party ad servers to help present advertisements online in connection with the Service, and/or web sites. These third party ad servers may use cookies or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not PlayPianu.com.Pianu does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Services and/or web sites may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies.

Third Parties’ Practices  
This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other providers of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies/people that Pianu.com does not own or control, or does not employ or manage.
